thenationalpages.co.uk 2010-05-27

# Privacy - The National Pages

##  Privacy Policy

**PROTECTING YOU AND YOUR INFORMATION**  
We understand that your information is private and as such we want to keep it that way. The National Pages will allow no access to your registration information to any third party organisation for any purpose. The National Pages are committed to protecting your privacy consistent with our obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998.

The National Pages **** reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice. To make sure that you are up to date with our policy please make sure you view it regularly. 

**PAYMENT METHODS**

We accept payment by online e-commerce, cheque or credit/debit card (via telephone). We accept the following credit or debit cards: Mastercard, Visa, Maestro, Switch and American Express (e-commerce only).

_Should you wish to pay by credit or debit card via telephone:_

  * We collect personal information from you related to your payment, such as your invoice number, name, address and credit/debit card details.
  * This information is not used for any other purpose than to service your payment.
  * All information you supply is treated with confidence and will not be shared with any other parties.
  * The National Pages does not store any financial information in relation to your payment, i.e. card details. 
  * Once your payment has been processed any such information is securely destroyed.  

_Should you wish to pay by online e-commerce:_

  * We use the secure online merchant services of the BarclayCard ePDQ system. 
  * All personal information related to your payment, such as your name, address and credit/debit card details are collected by the BarclayCard ePDQ system. 
  * This information is not used for any other purpose than to service your payment. 
  * All information you supply is treated with confidence and will not be shared with any other parties. 
  * The National Pages does not store any financial information in relation to your payment, i.e. card details. 

**COOKIES**  
The National Pages.co.uk uses cookies to make your experience with us easier. The cookies on this site are used to quicken your login process by clicking the ‘remember me’ checkbox for example.

The information stored in the cookie, which is encrypted and located on your hard drive is only what you have provided us with. This cookie cannot be used to retrieve any information from your computer and only works according with The National Pages.co.uk.

**INFORMATION STORAGE AND SECURITY**  
Your information is placed on a secure dedicated webserver. We have done all that we can to stop any unauthorised access to your information, although we and other website operators cannot guarantee that this information will be totally secure. 

**SEARCH USERS**   
There is no need to give The National Pages any personal information to use our service. Information will be gathered about general usage to enhance user experience and to give you the best services we can. We may ask for personal details when filling out questionnaires, competition entries and feedback forms and may contain separate terms and conditions, we can only do this with your expressed permission. 

Information will be gathered in order to see trends and usage to help keep the site up to date but no personal information will be used to improve our service.

When contacting The National Pages, users should be aware that comments/queries received via telephone or email may be monitored to make sure that users have the right experience with The National Pages.

**YOUR CONSENT**  
Registering with The National Pages gives us your consent to the collection and use of the information you have provided us with as described above, and thereof the information we may have for you and or your company. After you have registered you are entitled to change your mind and stop some if not all of the services The National Pages has to offer by calling or emailing us.
